allgamesfree.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy | All Games Free

  * LOGIN
  * SIGNUP

MOST **POPULAR**

[Home](http://www.allgamesfree.com/ "Home") / **Privacy Policy**

The following is the official privacy policy for www.allgamesfree.com , a website centered around kid’s games with child-friendly content, suitable for children and teens. This Privacy Policy covers issues related to personal information collected by the site and information regarding tracking and information collection from our affiliates, advertisers and partners.

Collection of Personal Information – At www.allgamesfree.com, we realize privacy of your personal information is very important and we try to keep you informed on how we collect, safeguard and use your personal data, where applicable. We never sell your personal information to third parties, however our site might run scripts (such as Google Analytics) that collect log file information for analytical and statistical reports. The kind of information these third parties collect include your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser you visit our site with, the pages you visit and the time you spend on pages of our site. This information is used strictly for ourselves, using it to better improve our site’s performance and user experience. We would never sell your personal information to third parties so never worry about that occuring.

We do run Google Adsense advertisements that are geared towards children and children’s games being we are in that world. If you ever see any inappropriate ads displayed on our site please have a guardian contact us so we may look into this immediately.

We do not collect personal information from children such as age, location, etc. We also do not employ chat rooms or private messaging services. If you would like any information regarding our website then please contact us. Please remember the internet can be a dangerous place for a child so be cautious and aware of where your child is spending his/her time.

Copyright – we have games in many different categories. The copyright of these games are the sole property of their creators and www.allgamesfree.com does not claim rights upon these games that are hosted on our servers. Gamer submitters agree that by submitting their game to us the physical file that is stored on our server is our property and that we may delete it, publish it or un-publish it without any previous announcement.

If you think that someone has stolen your gaming creation please use contact us immediately notifying us of the potential copyright abuse and we will take immediate action to delete the game and report it to the proper authorities.

By playing on AllGamesFree.com and using this website, you are thereby consenting with this Privacy Policy and you agree that you could be banned without any warnings if you are reported to missuse any of our privacy policy rules and terms. If you do not agree with our privacy policy we would suggest that you stop using our website. You also agree that we may at any time change the contents of this Privacy Policy without any announcement. Thank you again for visiting with us.

Copyright © 2016 All Games Free - All Rights Reserved [spielaffe](http://www.spielaffespielen.com/ "spielaffe") [spielaffe](http://www.spielaffen.blogspot.de/ "spielaffe") [spiele](http://www.facebookspiele.net/ "spiele") [spiele](http://www.spielex.net/ "spiele")
